Guide to the Grigori Mints Papers SC1225
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Subject files
  - Logical Ideal, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Modal Logic, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Modal Logic Genint, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Schwichtenberg, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Students, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Summer Project, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Tinker, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Teaching, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Teach, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Ergod Articles, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Zadachnik, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Workshop, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Wollic, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - VPUE Grant, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Visitors, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Travel, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Logic Seminar, 2010-2011 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Seminars, 2011-2012 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Seminars, 2008-2010 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Seminars, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Seminar Talks, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Seminars, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Sabbatical, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Pohlers, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Rusgrant, 2003/2013 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Reviews Ref. Report, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Rumfit, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Rayo, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Rathjen, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Queiroz, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Prawitz, undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Sasha, 2007-2010 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Sasha, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Sasha, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Topics in Logic: An Introduction to Proof Mining, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Pratt, Scott L. Hist. 94 Schroder-Heister, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Sazonov, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Schutte, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Schein, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Powers, Thomas M. Hist. 94 Schellinx, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Rybakov, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - MTA, 1999-2001 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - PT 2005 II (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - PT 2005 I (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - PT05 Lect, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Logic 2, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - PT05 Lect, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - MTA 06 Transpar, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Fresh 06, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - PHILMATH, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Berkeley Set Theory, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - MTA 06, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - General Interest, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Rec. Theory, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Topics, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Topics, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Topics 354, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - General Interest, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Topics Transp., 2010 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - TR, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Gen. Interest, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Sasha, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Truth, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Linguistics, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Sasha, 2004-2006 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Mathematical Documents, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Chang & Keisler, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Bag of Proofs, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - International Conference Tableaux, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - The Ergodic Theoretical Proof of Szemeredi's Theorem, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - A Formalization of Principle-Based Conception of Modality, 2/6/2003 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Interplay Between Proof Theory and Constructivist Ideology in the USSR, 1950-1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Completeness of Indexed e-Calculus, 6/1/2002 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Extensions of the Substitution Mehod to Impredicative Systems, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Semantical Analysis of Induitionalistic Logic, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Contributions of G. Takeuti, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Intuitionistic Frege Systems Are Polynomially Equivalent, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Topological Semantics of Propositional Int, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Substitution Method for Subsystems of Analysis, 10/22/1993 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Skolen and Epsilon Substitution Method, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Effective Content of Non-Effective Proofs, 6/1/2006 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Effective Proofs and Existence in Mathematics, 5/4/2006 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Review of Logical Aspects of Computation: Contributions and Distractions, 10/4/2006 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Existential Instantiation for Intuistionistic Logic, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Proof Theory and Consistency Proofs, 2/27/2005 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Normalization in the First Order e-Calculus, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Best Approximation in L1, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Lecture Slides, undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Hard Analysis: New Life of Old Ideas, 10/12/2010 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Describing the Ordinal of Mathematical Analysis, 5/19/2010 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Epsilon Substitution Method, 2010, Mar. 17-18 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Fixing Frege, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Epsilon Substitution Method for ID1, Jan. 17-18 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Three Faces of Natural Deduction, undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Sequent Formulation, undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - A Simple Substitution Method for ID1, 20 Mar. (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - A Proof of Topological Completeness for S4C in Cantor Space, 17 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - A Simple Proof of Strong Normalization w/ Permutative Conversions, undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Epsilon Substitution Method, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Dynamic Topological Logic, undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - The Logic of Continuous Transformations, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Problems Around e-Calculus, undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Strong Termination for the Epsilon Substitution Method, undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - The Undecidability of Dynamical Topological Logics, undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Intuitionistic Frege Systems Are Polynomially Equivalent, 2/24/2004 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Natural Deduction and its Neighbors, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Uniqueness Proofs in Approximation Theory, undated (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - A New Construction of Interpolants, 5/21/2002 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - A Mild Extension of First Order Predicate Logic, undated (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous Proofs, undated (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Reformulation in e-Language, undated (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - A Review of Effective Bounds on Strong Unicity in L1-Approximation, 4/16/2002 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Define a Node, undated (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Sets, undated (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - A Gentzen-style Formulation of the System B, undated (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Tran5P 10, undated (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Decidable Theories, 2013 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Failure of Interpolation in the Intuitionistic Logic of Constant Domains, 3/6/2012 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Mathematical Logic, undated (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Decidable Second Order Theories, 5/31/2011 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Countable Version of Omega-Rule, 5/17/2011 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Tantu, 2011 Jun. 15-17 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Elementary Intuitionistic Theories, undated (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Set Theory, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Decidable Second Order Theories Transpar, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Category Theory and Structural Proof Theory, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Bslid. tex, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Hard Analysis: New Life of Old Ideas, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Abstract, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - New Trends in Foundations of Mathematics, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Reduction to Theories of Lower Order, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Transpar, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Transpar, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Incomplete Proofs and Program Synthesis, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - A Review by G Mints of W. Buszkowski, Methematical Linguistics, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Transpar, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Transparencies, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Transpar, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Transpar 2, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Transpar, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Transpar, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Transpar, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Transparencies, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Logic Exercises, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - E Class, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - EPS06 Class, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - TR Girard WDW, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Fresh 07, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Constructive Math 351 B, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - A Formalization of Principle-Based Conception of Modality, 12/16/2002 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - An Accelerated e-Substitution Method, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - An e-Sub Method for Arithmetic with Predicates, 2/22/2001 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - A New e-Substitution Method for CR, Nov. 1999 - Aug. 2000 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - A New Construction of Interpolants, 5/21/2002 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - A Note of Completeness of an Epsilon Substitution Calculus, 1/26/1995 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - A Proof of a Theorem by Ikeda and Arai, 11/1/1995 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - A Simple Strong Normalization Proof with E and V, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - A Syntactic Proof of a Preservation Result, 1/21/2001 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Boolean Equations, 3/23/1999 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Conservation over PRA, 3/14/1994 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Continuity Theorem for Effective Operators in Metric Spaces, 11/19/1996 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Cut Elimination for Provability Logic, 4/30/2005 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - EPSCORRESP, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Extension of e-Substitution Method to ID1, 1/6/2006 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Finite Model Property for S4C, 2/10/2006 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Hilbert's Program and the Substitution Method, 1/12/1998 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Hilbert's Substitution Method, 5/3/1994 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Modulation and Interpolation, 10/17/2002 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Natural Deduction and Normalization for Quantified Modal Logic w/ Equality, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Normalization as an e-Substitution Process, 11/15/1994 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Normalizing IS4, 2/20/1998 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Normalization Proof for Derivations in PA After P. Cohen, 7/10/1997 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - On Maslov's Inverse Method, 12/2/1997 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Partial Proofs and Cut-Introduction, 1/11/1999 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Proof Search Under Shanin, 5/13/1999 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Quine and Modality, undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Resolution Rule for Diagrams, undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Simplified Strong Normalization Proof for Logic with Existence, 7/22/1997 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Solving Equations in Modal Logic, 3/1/2007 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Strong Normalization for Infinite, 5/8/1997 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Tait-Style Strong, 9/12/1997 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Topology and Logic, 8/12/2004 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Work of A.A. Markov on Stepwise Semantics, 11/14/2002 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Cut Elimination for S4C, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Relationship Between Proof Theory and Model Theory, 4/21/2003 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Abstracts, 2002-2006 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - A Completeness Proof for Propositional S4, 9/24/2002 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - An Approach to an e-Substitution Method, undated (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - An e-Substitution Method for Predicate Logic, 6/13/1994 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - A Proof of Topological Completeness for S4, undated (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - A Termination Proof for e-Substitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Axiomatization of a Skolem Function, undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Chapter OTL, undated (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Classical MLL = IMLL, 9/7/1999 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Completeness of Indexed e-Calculus, undated (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - A Completeness Proof for Propositional S4, 7/14/1995 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Cut Elimination for a Simple Formulation of Epsilon Calculus, undated (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Cut Elimination for Simple Type Theory with an Axiom, 10/1/1997 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Dynamic Topological Logic, 3/19/2004 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Epsilon-Substitution Method for Ramified Language and Comprehension Rule, 12/30/1994 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Existential Instantiation and Strong Normalization, 1/27/1997 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Extended Normal Form Theorem for Logical Proofs from Axioms, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Incomplete Prioofs and Program Synthesis, Extended Abstract, 1/10/2002 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Indexed Systems of Sequents and Cut-Elimination, 10/12/1995 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Interpolation, undated (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Intuitionistic Frege Systems Are Polynomially Equivalent, 8/5/2004 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Linear Terms, undated (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Notes on Constructive Negation, undated (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Propositional Logic of Continuous Transformations in Cantor Space, 12/9/2004 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Quick Cut-Elimination for Monotone Cuts, 2001 Apr. (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Reductions of Finite and Infinite Derivatives, 4/19/1999 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Reductions to Theories of Lower Order, 5/7/1996 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Russell Anticipation of Intuitionistic Logic, undated (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - S4 is Topologically Complete for R, undated (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Skolemization and Quick Cut-Elimination, undated (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Strong Termination for the Epsilon Substitution Method, 10/10/1995 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Terminating Epsilon Substitution, undated (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - The Complexity of the Disjunction and Existence, 8/11/1998 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - The Epsilon Substitution Method and Continuity, undated (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Thor Skolem, undated (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Three Faces of Natural Deduction, 6/27/1997 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Topological Completeness of Propositional Int, 6/14/2000 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Transfer of Sequent, 2/3/1995 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Proof Search Tree and Cut-Elimination, 8/8/2007 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Logical Equations in Monadic Logic, 8/8/2007 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Unwinding a Non-Effective Cut-Elimination Proof, undated (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Letters to Answer, undated (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Letters, undated (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Kriesel, undated (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Stanford, undated (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Grad Students, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Interpolation, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - IGPL-JLC, 2010 Apr. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Help to Russia, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Guests, 7/17/2006 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Grad Workshop, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Log Prog, 2006-2011 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Logic Program, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - LMH, 2005-2009 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Maslovs, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Markov, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Masters, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Log Seminar, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Lists, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Log Search, 2001-2005 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Logic Lunch, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Logic Flyer, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Past Conferences, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Notes of Talks (Others), 9/4/2001 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Meetings, 2001-2005 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Quine, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - PT Workshop, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Problems, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Serger, 8/28/2006 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Proof Mining, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Constructive Math Topics, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Banalytic, undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Ebar, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Conference, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Cade Tutorial, undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - ASL Reviews, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - AMS Notices, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Annual Report, 2009-2011 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - AMS Notices, undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Aslo, 2005-2014 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Historically important diss with GM notes + comments, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Natural Deduction + notes, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Russia textbook important in his field, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Programming book important in his work + notes, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Predilation analysis, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Inscription to GM, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Very rare Georgian logician + Georgian publishing company, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Standard Russian textbook in Math Logic, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Bibliography that includes GM papers, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Inscription + notes, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Popular lecture in its original form, 1979-1982 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Maslov translated from The French, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - By GM and Maslov, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - GM notations pg 216, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Contains paper by GM: special book or topic, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - by Novikov Math Logic early textbook in the field, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Textbook Algebra, geometry with intuitionistic logic insert, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Theories for Admissible Sets: A Unifying Approach to Proof Theory, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - GM's well used copy of this important text, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Extensive notes, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Fraenkel and Bar-Hillel Text on Set Theory in Russian with extensive card of notes and extensive annotation, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - K. Schutte Proof Theory + Notes, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Hilbert's tenth problem, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - MOCKBA MNP + extensive notes, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Girard - Dissertationes Mathematicae + extensive notes, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Kreisel, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - The Problems of Philosophy: Third Edition, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Constructive Math, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Famous Mathematica - G.M. Edition, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Institute of Imformatics Systems, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Abstracts and Resumes, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Early G.M. Papers, 1966-1967 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Grisha an Editor, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Inscription, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - A History of Philosophy and Logic in Russia, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Theory of Algorithms, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - G.M. Papers, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - G.M.'s Notations, 1995-2013 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Annals of Pure and Applied Logic, 2005, May. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Information and Computation, 2009, Oct. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - First Order Modal Logic, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Abstacts, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Papers, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - VITAS (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - VITA etc., 1997 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Archive Trips etc., 1992 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - History, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - CSLI, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - J. Ayers, 10/1/2001 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Anna, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Days SPB, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Cohen, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Freidson, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Hohmas, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - ICM, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Kestrel, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Kremer, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - LLC 01, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Maslova, 1997-1999 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Markov Volume, 1997-2000 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Nog, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Onthologies, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Orevkov, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Proof Checking, 1994-1996 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Proposal, 1995-2000 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Rybakov, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Satisfiability, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Seminars, 1991-2000 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Seregine, undated (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Smirnov, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Soros, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Springer Files, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Summa, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Talks Mine, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Techn Report, CSLI, 11/15/1994 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Tests (General), 1993 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Travel, 1992-2001 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Vassilyer, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Visitors, 1996-1998 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Visits (Past), 1998 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Workshop 2K, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Zaslavsky, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Epsilon Calculus with Applications, 3/13/2010 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Journals, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Survery, Proof Theory, 1970-1979 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Model Th. B, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - 160B, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Model Theory, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - 160B, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - 290B Model Theory B, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Proof Theory B, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - M294, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Rec. Theory B, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Recursion Theory, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - M294, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Topics in Logic, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Tekctb1, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Philosophy 159, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - 160B, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - 160B, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - 160B, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - 160A, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - 160A Math Logic, 1987 & 1992 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Negation 2000 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - M294, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Proof Theory B, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Proof Theory, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Logic Seminar, Spring 2001 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Modal Logic, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Etch, undated (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - 160B, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - 160B, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Model Theory A, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Model Theory A, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - 160B, gg, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Proof Theory, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Proof Theory, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Proof Theory A98, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - PTB2001 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - MTB 2000 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - MTB 02, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - PT 02, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - 160A 2001 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - 160A 2000 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Proof Theory, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - M290B Model Theory B, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Proof Theory B, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - The System ID, undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Proof Theory B, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Small Collection of Business Cards on G.M.'s desk, undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Center For the Study of Language and Information, undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Cut-elimination and Normal Forms of Sequent Derivations, 1994, Nov. (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Grigori Mints - bio, cv, etc., undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Proofs, Categories and Computations - Essays in Honor of Grigori Mints, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Reviews, Evaluations, undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - PHIL162/262, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - TRUTH13N, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Logic 1, undated (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Logic Berkeley, undated (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Bounded Arithmetic, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Absoluteness of Intuitionistic Logic, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Recurrence in Ergodic Theory and Combinatorial Number Theory, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Logic Colloquium, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Essays Dedicated to Johan van Benthem on the Occasion of his 50th Birthday, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Das Kontinuum, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Problems of Reducing the Exhaustive Search, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Theoretical Computer Science, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Constraint Programming, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Godel Remembered, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Programming Logic, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Computers and Artifical Intelligence, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Estonian Academy of Sciences Yearbook, 2008-2009 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Mathematical Logic, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Notre Dame Journal of Formal Logic, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Journal of Philosophical Logic, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Proof Theory of Modal Logic, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Formalizing the Dynamics of Information, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Games, Logic, and Constructive Sets, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Vicious Circles, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Studia Logica, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Thinking About Mathematics, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Machine Intelligence, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 23)